A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87)
1961-1987
1970-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA479
522.69 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1983-1987.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: project and fellowship material.
Public health administration; Public health -- Education; Philanthropy -- United States; Public health; Nursing; Philanthropy; Medical sciences; Natural history; Arts; Agriculture; Charities; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Epidemiology; Epidemics; Hospitals; Hookworm disease; Scholarships; Scarlatina -- Hospitals -- Administration; Public health -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Life sciences; Malaria; Humanities; Humanities -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Social sciences -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Tuberculosis; Medical care; Social sciences; Yaws; Yellow fever; Viruses -- Research; War relief
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 83), 1961-1991; 1970-1982; 1.9; 90.59 Cubic Feet; 224 letter-size document boxes, 10 legal-size document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, 1 half-legal document box, and 1 15-11.5 oversized document box
  Arrangement
  Arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Files transferred to RAC by the Rockefeller Foundation, 1983 (July 1983 and later).
  - International, 100
    - Films, 1941, 1943-1946, 1948-1953, 1955, 1967, 1969-1972, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Population - Conference, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Population - Conference (Bellagio I), 1969-1970, 1983, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Population - Conference (Bellagio II), 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6, Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Population - Conference (Bellagio III), 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
    - Population - Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 2, Folder 10-12, Box 3, Folder 13-15)
    - Tapes, 1972-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
  - Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT) International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 105
    - Administration, 1969-1979 (Box 4, Folder 19-22)
    - Administration - Central Files, 1970-1973, 1976, 1978, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 24, Box 5, Folder 25-27)
    - Board of Directors: Supplementary Material (Box 5, Folder 28-30, Box 6, Folder 31-36, Box 7, Folder 37-41)
    - Ferroni, Marco A., 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
    - Financial, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 44-46)
    - Financial: Supplementary Material (Box 8, Folder 47, Box 9, Folder 48-51, Box 10, Folder 52-55)
    - Maize Chromosomes, 1975-1977 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Maize Chromosomes: Supplementary Material (Box 11, Folder 57-58)
    - Organization and Planning, 1966-1967, 1969-1979 (Box 11, Folder 59-60, Box 12, Folder 61-64)
    - Organization and Planning: Supplementary Material (Box 12, Folder 65-66, Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Personnel, 1968, 1971-1976 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Publicity and Reports, 1975-1981 (Box 13, Folder 69-71, Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Publicity and Reports: Supplementary Material (Box 14, Folder 73-75)
    - Tripp, Robert, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 76, Box 15, Folder 77)
    - CIMMYT - Turkish Wheat Project, 1966-1967, 1976; 804
      - Wheat Improvement, 1966-1967, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 78-80)
      - Wheat Improvement - Administration, 1970-1983 (Box 15, Folder 81-82, Box 16, Folder 83-85)
      - Wheat Improvement - Agreements, 1967-1971, 1974, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 86)
      - Wheat Improvement - Financial, 1967-1968, 1970-1982 (Box 16, Folder 87-88)
      - Wheat Improvement - Organization and Planning, 1968-1982 (Box 17, Folder 89-93, Box 18, Folder 94-99, Box 19, Folder 100-101)
      - Wheat Improvement - Organization and Planning (Evaluation), 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 102)
      - Wheat Improvement - Publicity and Reports, 1966, 1968-1978, 1981-1984 (Box 19, Folder 103-105, Box 20, Folder 106)
      - "Analysis and Evaluation of Land Reform Activities in Turkey" by Prof. Dr. Resat Aktan, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 107)
      - "Mechanization of Agriculture in Turkey" by Resat Aktan, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 108)
        General
        Article in "Land Economics",a quarterly journal of Planning, Housing and Public Utilities, Volume XXXIII, Number 4, November 1957
      - "Incentive and Welfare Effects of Tax Structure Change: The Case of Turkey" by Kenan Bulutoğlu, undated (Box 20, Folder 109)
      - "Buğday Sorunu", 1974 September (Box 20, Folder 110)
        Wheat Problem
      - Course Handouts, undated (Box 20, Folder 111-112)
      - Marginal Cost Pricing, undated (Box 20, Folder 113)
      - "Small Farmer Credit in Turkey" by Thomas Stickley and Suha Satana, 1972 November (Box 20, Folder 114)
      - "Land Reform in Turkey" by Edwin J. Cohn, 1970 June (Box 20, Folder 115)
        Agency for International Development Spring Review
      - Inputs - Weed Control, 1967, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 116)
      - Maps (Box 20, Folder 117)
      - "Capital and Finance in Turkish Agriculture" by James E. Blalock, 1969 May (Box 20, Folder 118)
      - "Review of the Turkish Corn Program", 1973 (Box 20, Folder 119)
      - "Estimated Wheat Projection and Marketing Costs on a 2,000-Acre Dryland Farm, Oregon Columbia Plateau", 1974 December (Box 21, Folder 120)
        Oregon State University Extension Service
      - "Use of Nitrogen Fertilizers in Wheat Production Under Dryland Conditions of Central Anatolia" by C. Nadir Izgin, 1975 April (Box 21, Folder 121)
      - "The Economics of Fertilizer Use on Wheat in the Dry Land Areas of Turkey" by Olan D. Forker, 1970 December (Box 21, Folder 122)
      - "Estimating the Value of the Poppy Crop, Compensation Costs and Investment Required to Replace Lost Income", undated (Box 21, Folder 123)
      - "Devaluation Theory - An Introduction" by Kenneth M. Kauffman, undated (Box 21, Folder 124)
      - "Conditions for Viability of the Turkish Economy: A Macro-Economic Analysis" by Kenneth M. Kauffman, undated (Box 21, Folder 125)
      - "Growth Models: Some Recent Applications to the Turkish Economy" by Kenneth M. Kauffman, undated (Box 21, Folder 126)
      - "Markets and Economic Growth" by Kenneth M. Kauffman, undated (Box 21, Folder 127)
      - "Some Technical Aspects of Exchange Rate Policy", undated (Box 21, Folder 128)
      - Field Trip Notes, 1972, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 129)
      - English-Turkish Glossary of Economic Terms, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 130)
      - "A Glossary of Agricultural Terms (English/Turkish, Turkish/English)", 1961 (Box 21, Folder 131)
      - "Thoughts on Integrated Rural Development Projects in a World Facing Food and Rural Poverty Crises" by John L. Fischer, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 132)
      - "Marginal Sector in the Process of Development, and the Turkish Case" by Ilhan Tekeli, 1974 July (Box 21, Folder 133)
      - "Changes in the Rural Structure of Turkey, Due to Agricultural Mechanization Within Market Conditions" by Ilhan Tekeli, undated (Box 21, Folder 134)
      - "The Draft Report of the Study Group for the Agricultural Development Project of Denizli Province", 1964 July (Box 21, Folder 135)
      - "Recommendations and Projections for the Turkish Fertilizer Industry" by John M. Hill, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 136)
      - "Agricultural Price Policy in Turkey", Volumes One and Two, by Olan D. Forker, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 137)
        United States Agency for International Development Economic Staff Papers, Discussion Paper No. 2
      - "Migration and Urban Social Structures" by Iris Kapil and Hasan Genҫağa, undated (Box 22, Folder 138)
        United States Agency for International Development Economic Staff Papers, Discussion Paper No. 1
      - "Wheat Production in Turkey" by Olan D. Forker, 1971 May (Box 22, Folder 139)
      - "A Treatise on the Timing of the Agriculture Price Support Announcement" by Olan D. Forker, 1970 November (Box 22, Folder 140)
      - Agriculture - Names, 1970-1971, 1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 141)
        Includes notebooks and photographs
      - Turkey Statistical Yearbook, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 142)
      - Topraksu Paper - Working Documents, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 143-144)
      - Backup Working Documents - Luxembourg and Topraksu Paper (Box 23, Folder 145-146)
      - Reports on Project 77-26 - Agricultural Advisory Group (Starch Group), 1950-1957 (Volume 1), 1963 August (Box 23, Folder 147-149, Box 24, Folder 150)
      - Miscellaneous Statistics and Reports, 1959-1971, 1974-1976 (Box 24, Folder 151)
      - Agricultural Statistics in Turkish and English, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 152-153)
      - Agricultural Structure and Production, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 154)
      - Economic and Social Indicators - Turkey, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 155)
      - Department of Environmental Technology - Wheat Project (Box 24, Folder 156)
      - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development - Agricultural Projections - Turkey, 1968 July (Box 24, Folder 157)
      - "Livestock in Turkey" by Don L. Good, 1971 April (Box 24, Folder 158)
      - "The Production Incentives Used in Turkish Agriculture" by Nevzat Karacahisarli, undated (Box 25, Folder 159)
      - "Use of Nitrogen Fertilizers in Wheat Production Under the Dryland Conditions of Central Anatolia" by C. Nadir Izgin, 1975 April (Box 25, Folder 160)
      - "Organization and Administration of Agricultural Research in Turkey" by Coyt T. Wilson, 1966 November (Box 25, Folder 161)
      - End of Tour Report by John M. Hill, 1971 July (Box 25, Folder 162)
      - "Laying the Foundation for a Strategy for Agricultural Development" by John L. Fischer, 1972 April (Box 25, Folder 163)
      - Spring Review of Small Farmer Credit, 1972 November (Box 25, Folder 164)
      - Weed Control C/B, 1971, 1973, 1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 165)
      - Demonstration Program Analysis, 1974-1975; undated (Box 25, Folder 166)
      - Wheat - Oregon State University/U.S. Agency for International Development Project, 1968-1970, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 167-168)
      - Wheat - Our Economic Program, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 169, Box 26, Folder 170-172)
      - U.S. Agency for International Development (USAID) and Other Published Reports and Documents
        - Directory of Participants 1949-1971 (Box 27, Folder 173)
        - Development of Agriculture in Turkey on a Time-Cost Schedule, 1961 April (Box 27, Folder 174)
        - Improving the Marketing of Fresh Fruits and Vegetables in Turkey by J. Kenneth Samuels, 1960 October (Box 27, Folder 175)
        - More Wheat From Fallow Farming, 1973, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 176)
          First edition, January 1973; Second edition, 1975
        - Emigrant Turkish Workers - A Framework for Analysis by Duncan R. Miller, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 177)
        - Prospects for Turkish Agriculture, 1966 December (Box 27, Folder 178)
          A Report by Study Team to the Minister of Agriculture, February 10, 1967
        - Mexican Wheat Comes to Turkey by L. M. Humphrey, 1969 April (Box 27, Folder 179)
        - In-Service Training Program for Activating Village Agricultural Committees - Consultants Final Report, 1969 July (Box 27, Folder 180)
        - Agricultural Planning in Turkey by Orlin J. Scoville, 1960 October (Box 27, Folder 181)
        - Me and My Job in Turkey by Technicians in Division of Food and Agriculture, 1962 October (Box 27, Folder 182)
        - The Adoption of New Bread Wheat Technology in Selected Regions of Turkey by Nazmi Demir, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 183)
        - Economic and Social Aspects of Farm Mechanization in Turkey, undated (Box 27, Folder 184)
        - MPM Wheat Study, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 185)
        - Turkey Country Development Brief, Food and Agriculture Sector, 1973 December (Box 28, Folder 186)
        - Trends in Turkish Agriculture, Graphs and Statistics 1938-1966, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 187)
        - Soil and Crop Management Research at the Wheat Research and Training Center, October 1970 to August 1973, by Floyd E. Bolton, 1973 August (Box 28, Folder 188)
        - Wheat Production Manual, undated (Box 28, Folder 189)
        - Discovering Anatolia, 1969 August (Box 28, Folder 190)
        - Agricultural Structure and Production, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 191)
        - Project for Supplying Credit to Farmers for On-Field Development Works and Developing Small Water Resources, undated (Box 28, Folder 192)
        - Tϋrikiye Tariminda Makro-Prodϋktivite (1950-1969) by Nazmi Demir, 1973 January (Box 28, Folder 193)
          Turkey in Agriculture Macro-Productivity
        - The Mass Media and Rural Development in Turkey, Report No. 3, Rural Development Research Project, by Frederick W. Frey, 1966 January (Box 29, Folder 194)
        - Farm Tools and Implements, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 195)
        - Agricultural Planning, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 196)
        - "Agricultural Price Intervention by the Government of Turkey" by Olan D. Forker, 1967 August (Box 29, Folder 197)
        - Gelír Dağilimi Araştirmasi 1973, 1976 September (Box 29, Folder 198)
          Income Distribution Research
        - "Agricultural Prices and Subsidies in Turkey" by G. P. Temple, 1976 July (Box 29, Folder 199)
        - The Turkish Administrator, A Cultural Survey, 1967 August (Box 29, Folder 200)
        - A.I.D. Assistance to Agriculture in Turkey by John R. Wilson, 1971 August (Box 29, Folder 201)
        - "A Ten-Year Program for the Development of Range Management in Turkey" by L. P. Short, undated (Box 30, Folder 202)
        - Research, Productivity and Economic Reports on Agriculture in Turkey by Leonard H. Rhodes, 1967 February-1969 May (Box 30, Folder 203)
          A compilation of reports written by Leonard H. Rhodes, Agriculture Economics Advisor, USAID Turkey, during his tour in Turkey, February 1967 through May 1969
        - "Cost and Benefits of Semi-Dwarf Wheat in Coastal Areas of Turkey" by Leonard H. Rhodes, 1967 October (Box 30, Folder 204)
        - "The Economics of Mexican Wheat in Turkey" by Leonard H. Rhodes, 1967 October (Box 30, Folder 205)
        - "A Simplified Approach to Agricultural Systems" by Milo L. Cox, 1970 May (Box 30, Folder 206)
        - A Program for the Years Ahead, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 207)
        - "People, Food and Cities in the Years Ahead" by Lewis S. Anderson, 1969 March (Box 30, Folder 208)
        - Reports on Visits to Turkey - Katherine Holtzclaw, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 209)
          February 15-March 14, 1953 and July 6-August 7, 1953 visits
        - "Comments on Land Reform in Turkey" by Raymond H. Davis, 1964 April (Box 30, Folder 210)
        - "Comments on American Aid to Agricultural Development in Turkey" by John D. Montgomery, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 211)
        - Agricultural Development in Turkey: Effect on Products Competitive with U.S. Farm Exports, 1958 January (Box 30, Folder 212)
        - Draft Report of the Agro-Industry Survey Team to the U.S. Economic Coordinator for CENTO Affairs, 1969 August (Box 30, Folder 213)
        - Adoption of Recommendations of the Agricultural Study Team in Turkey, November-December 1966, 1968 April (Box 30, Folder 214)
        - Pesticide Situation of Turkey, 1958 January (Box 30, Folder 215)
        - Table 1 - Fruits and Vegetables Growing in Various Regions of Turkey, undated (Box 30, Folder 216)
        - Program, Schedule of Operations and Required Organization for Improved Plant Protection in Turkey, undated (Box 30, Folder 217)
        - "The Status of Farm Mechanization" by C. D. Busch, undated (Box 30, Folder 218)
        - "Agriculture" by O. J. Wheatley, 1964 March (Box 30, Folder 219)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 220)
        - Polatli, Keskin (Ankara) ve Kulu (Konya) İlҫelerinde Buğday Uretiminin Ekonomik Analizi, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 221)
          Wheat Production Economic Analysis
        - 1955-1970 Yillari Arasinda Buğday Uretiminde Izlenen ̬Çikti-Girdi Ilişkileri, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 222)
          Wheat Production Output-Input Relationships Monitored Between the Years 1955-1970
      - Cigdem's Biblio Cards, undated (Box 30, Folder 223)
      - Fulbright Directory, undated (Box 31, Folder 224)
      - Agricultural Structure and Production, 1969-1973 (Box 31, Folder 225-227)
      - Census of Agriculture - Sample Survey Results, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 228)
      - "Introduction of Improved Wheat Technology in Turkey" by Oddvar Aresvik, undated (Box 32, Folder 229)
      - Selected Agricultural Statistics in Ranked Order for Countries of the Near East Region, 1973 August (Box 32, Folder 230)
      - A Socio-Economic Study of Farming in Denizli Province, 1967 January (Box 32, Folder 231)
      - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development - The Development of Agriculture in Turkey, 1969 December (Box 32, Folder 232)
      - The Economic Development of Turkey, Volume III: Major Social and Economic Sectors, 1974 April (Box 32, Folder 233)
      - The Economic Development of Turkey, Volume V: Statistical Appendix, 1974 April (Box 32, Folder 234)
      - Appraisal of An Agricultural Credit and Agroindustries Project Turkey, 1976 April (Box 32, Folder 235)
      - Appraisal of Third Livestock Development Project Turkey, 1976 May (Box 32, Folder 236)
      - Letters from Turkey, Richard D. Robinson, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 237)
        Reprinted for the Peace Corps by Permission of The Institute for Current World Affairs
      - "After the Green Revolution" by John L. Fischer, undated (Box 33, Folder 238)
      - "Impacts from Rapidly Changing Technology in Turkish Agriculture (Implications for Planning)" by Nazmi Demir, 1972 November (Box 33, Folder 239)
      - Bitkisel Uretim - Girdi Iliskileri Uzerinde Ekonomik Analizler by Nazmi Demir et al., 1971 November (Box 33, Folder 240)
        Vegetable Production - Entry Relationships on Economic Analyses
      - Turkiye Tariminda Makro-Produktivite by Nazmi Demir, 1973 January (Box 33, Folder 241)
      - Turkiye'de Tarimsal Planlama Calismalari (Girdi-Cikti Analizleri Ile Tuketim Projeksiyonlari), 1977, I. Rapor by Nazmi Demir et al., 1974 January (Box 33, Folder 242)
        Agricultural Planning in Turkey (Input-Output Projections of Consumption), 1977, Report No. 1
      - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development - The Agricultural Economy of Turkey: Problems and Policies, 1970 January (Box 33, Folder 243)
      - Unofficial Translations and Summaries of Selected Sections and Tables of the Third Five-Year Development Plan (1973-1977) - Turkey, 1973 January (Box 33, Folder 244)
        Fourth Section - Sector Developments; Chapter Two - Agriculture (paras. 407-522)
      - Turkey - Irrigated Agriculture: Proposal and Recommendations for the Review of the Capital Projects Advisory Committee, undated (Box 33, Folder 245)
      - "A Programming Approach to Agricultural Policy Planning in West Pakistan" by Carl H. Gotsch, 1967 September (Box 33, Folder 246)
      - "The Production Incentives Used in Turkish Agriculture" by Nevzat Karacahisarli, undated (Box 33, Folder 247)
      - Estimates of Foodgrain Production and Marketings From Input Estimates, India, 1949/50 to 1973/74 and Projections to 1983/84 by John W. Mellor et al., 1975 September (Box 34, Folder 248)
      - Changes in the Composition of Capital, Employment, Value Added and Production in Various Industry Groups, India, 1951-1965 by Uttam Dabholkar and Arthur Goldsmith, 1975 October (Box 34, Folder 249)
      - Small-Farmer Development Strategies: A Seminar Report by Dale W. Adams and E. Walter Coward, Jr., 1972 July (Box 34, Folder 250)
      - Marketing Problems Associated with Small Farm Agriculture by Kelly Harrison and Kenneth Shwedel, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 251)
      - Allocation of Authority in Land Reform Programs: A Comparative Study of Administrative Processes and Outputs by John D. Montgomery, 1974 March (Box 34, Folder 252)
      - The Economics of Farm Mechanization and Processing in Developing Countries by Gordon Gemmill and Carl Eicher, 1973 December (Box 34, Folder 253)
      - Chapter 28 - Integrated Rural Development by Uma Lele, undated (Box 34, Folder 254)
      - Handout for "A View of the Plan Puebla: An Application of Hierarchical Decision Models" by Christina H. Gladwin, 1976 August (Box 34, Folder 255)
      - "Technical Change, Labor Use and Small Farmer Development: Evidence from Sierra Leone" by Dunstan S. C. Spencer and Derek Byerlee, 1976 August (Box 34, Folder 256)
      - "Relationships Among Variables" Taken from Agricultural Market Prices, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 257)
      - Macro Economic Analysis and Justification of AID Local Currency Financing, undated (Box 34, Folder 258)
      - "Increasing Agricultural Productivity - Economic and Social Effects: A Planning Perspective" by John L. Fischer, undated (Box 34, Folder 259)
      - "Analysis of Wheat Data From Turkey: Progress Report" by O. P. Engelstad, 1972 January (Box 34, Folder 260)
      - "The State of Agriculture and Agricultural Planning in Turkey (1972-1972)" by Nevzat Karacahisarli, 1972 November (Box 34, Folder 261)
      - Miscellaneous Reports, 1973, undated (Box 34, Folder 262)
  - International Potato Program (IPP), 107
    - International Potato Program - Peru, 331
      - Rhoades, Robert E., 1976-1983 (Box 34, Folder 263-265, Box 35, Folder 266-267)
  - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT), 110
    International Center for Tropical Agriculture
    - Administration, 1970-1979 (Box 35, Folder 268-270)
    - Bean Pathology, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 271)
    - Board of Trustees, 1970-1977, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 272-276)
    - Board of Trustees: Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 277-279)
    - Financial, 1970-1979 (Box 37, Folder 280-282, Box 38, Folder 283)
    - Financial: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 38, Folder 284-287, Box 39, Folder 288-289)
    - Organization and Planning, 1970-1979 (Box 39, Folder 290-292, Box 40, Folder 293-294)
    - Pachico, Douglas H., 1978-1982 (Box 40, Folder 295-297)
    - Personnel, 1966-1976 (Box 40, Folder 298, Box 41, Folder 299-301)
    - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) - Latin America, 300
      - Rice, 1966-1973, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 302-304)
      - Rice: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 42, Folder 305-306)
  - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD), 112
    - Financial, 1973-1975 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 307)
    - Financial: Supplementary Material, undated (Box 42, Folder 308)
    - Organization and Planning, 1965, 1969-1979 (Box 42, Folder 309-311, Box 43, Folder 312-316, Box 44, Folder 317-321)